appearoo.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy - appearoo

## The essence of our Privacy Policy

**1) US-EU Safe Harbor Framework support  
**Society3 is supporting and in compliance with the [US-EU Safe Harbor Framework](http://export.gov/safeharbor/index.asp "Link to the official site at export.gov").

**2) Information disclosure**  
We will NOT sell or otherwise distribute any of your personal information to any third party without your specific and individual approval.

**3) Data visibility control**  
You are in control of the visibility of your personal [contact](http://go.appearoo.com/contact/) information (email, phone numbers, IM etc.).

**4) Data ownership**  
You own your personal information and have the right to export and transfer it to any place you wish including any other network.

**5) Meta data usage**  
We reserve the right to use so called “meta data” from activities on our system. Meta data never include any personal information such as name, email address or IP address.

**6) Security**  
We use secure login encryption and we do encrypt all passwords stored on Society3. Our team will never ask you for a password and is not able to decrypt or retrieve passwords for you.

## The Privacy Policy

**General Statement**  
While visiting our general web site Society3.com or XeeMe.com, we do not collect or require any personal information. If you are using our services such as any of our online applications, we do require users to register and ask you to provide personal and business profile information. The nature of all Society3 social [media](http://go.appearoo.com/media/) applications is to publicly share social presence information. However it is up to you to define the level of exposure of your personal information and who shall have access to that information. By default no email addresses or birthday personal is exposed to anybody, yet your name and photo as well as title or company relationship is publicly visible.

**Support of the Respect Trust Framework**  
This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference the Respect Trust Framework listed with the [Open Identity Exchange](http://openidentityexchange.org/trust-frameworks/respect-trust-framework) The purpose of the Respect Trust Framework is to define a simple set of principles and rules to which all Members of a digital trust network agree so that they may share identity and personal data with greater confidence that it will be protected and only used as authorized. Society3 and all Members of the Respect Network agree to operate under the Respect Trust Framework.

**Collecting Personal Information**  
Society3 may collect certain personal information from you when you use our services. You have the choice to answer or decline almost any of the information except your first name, last name, your personal email address and your business email address. Your name will be used to introduce you to others or be identified in your network of business people you selected to collaborate with. Your personal email address is exclusively used to access the Society3 system and/or request a lost password. Unless you explicitly provide that email address to others it is not available for contacting you by anybody within Society3. Your business email address is used to send you introductions or allow other users who you invited or confirmed their invitation to contact you. None of your email addresses is available to any other user, than the one you have a confirmed relationship or confirmed alliance with.

**Data we store**  
We store registration data including your user name, email address and IP Addresses. We collect data from a variety of activities and transactions, mainly to develop your social capital value report. We store all the information you provide about yourself, as a representative of your company and data you provide for business activities. We also store all connections you create, networks you develop and activities you perform with those networks. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Society3 applications is considered a violation of Society3 terms of services and should be brought to our attention.

**Usage of Cookies**  
We are using so called “cookies”, small information bits to store application relevant information in your browser. Using the application requires that the use of cookies is enabled. You can review the content of the cookie data at any time in your browser. We do not store email addresses or passwords in cookies.

**Personal Information Disclosure**  
We will not sell or otherwise distribute any of your personal information to any third party without your specific and individual approval. At this stage there is no plan or reason to ever even ask you for such approval. Society3 and all application users of our services usually use applications to build, maintain and grow their business relationships and therefore we provide your personal information to those contacts you contact or agree to be connected with. If you reject a connection request, your personal contact will not be exposed, forwarded or otherwise available to such or any other user.  
As you upload your personal contacts to Society3 applications, you decide which of such contacts you want to invite into your network on a contact by contact basis. The contacts you select to invite will be contacted by Society3 or XeeMe to join your network. You may choose not to invite selected contacts for whatever reason. Those not invited contacts are considered “loose” contacts and neither invited nor contacted by Society3. But those contacts may also exist in other connections within Society3 applications and therefore be invited by others or contacted by Society3 through other sources.  
An active user in Society3 has the option to provide visibility to his or her personal contact information only to their confirmed contacts and alliances (default) or only to their contacts but to alliances or to everybody within Society3. Names, picture and general business relationship information including company name, public company contact information and the users business profile is available to every Society3 user. Every user has the option to add additional information to their contacts (Personal notes). That information is only visible to that particular user, not to the contact or anybody else.

**Sharing your information with third parties**  
We DO NOT share any of your personal information, in particular email address or age with third parties.

**You sharing information with third parties**  
You are prohibited to share any of your information in Society3 with any third party for whatever reason. You are further prohibited to share your account access information with any other person that may access your account for marketing or any other purpose, other than technically servicing your account.

**Links inside Society3**  
Society3 provides ways for users or user organizations to expose links to their websites or links to documents and other sites. We request users to not use those links to point to any unlawful or any politically incorrect or socially not appropriate sites or documents. While we undertake our best effort to maintain a high level of ethics, we cannot guarantee that inappropriate links will exist.

**Data Ownership**  
users own their personal data and have the right to alter, export or delete that information at any time. As data get provided to confirmed connections, the user has the ability to decide whether such data can be exported by their connections and used for other purposes like address books or others networks etc. As personal connections may be shared by a person with their employer for the purpose of lead development, such contacts will become part of the company’s data.  
Corporate users (companies) own their business data such as business opportunities, company profiles or employee lists. As such data get shared with confirmed partners or alliances, the company agrees that such shared data can be used by its alliance in any way or shape or based on contractual regulations outside Society3. Any process of sharing cannot be reversed, other than by regulations outside Society3.

**Social Graph Ownership**  
Our definition of “Social Graph”: The social graphs are relationship maps describing the connection points between entities (organizations or individuals) and their respective activities between such relationships. Activities between connections may be tracked and aggregated to develop reports such as the Social Capital Value. Society3 invented a series of rules, algorithms and processes to calculate values and provide corresponding reports. Those rules, processes and algorithms as well as the resulting data are owned by Society3. Each user has the right to use and communicate their own results in any way they wish. However users are prohibited to export or otherwise distribute the underlying data that may contain references to other user (companies or individuals).

**Access Security**  
Society3 is committed to protect our user’s privacy. No Society3 employee will ever ask you for your password. Passwords are highly encrypted and we do not provide any way to decrypt such passwords. If a password gets lost you will need to request a new password. We will not use your personal email address in any way, other than sending you a lost password. We also do not provide your personal email address to any of your connections, unless you decide to do so. All communication is performed using your business email address.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Society3 reserves the right to introduce changes to this privacy policy with 30 days notice. Any change of our privacy policy will give users the right to immediately cancel their contract with full reimbursement of pre paid subscription for the remainder of the subscription period and to remove all their information from the system.
